Contact

Lagos 08100144840 (Home) francenemuo@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/franc-enemuo (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Tailwind CSS

Git

React.js

Languages

English (Full Professional)

French (Elementary)

Igbo (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Android Basic

Responsive Web Design

ADVANCED STYLING WITH RESPONSIVE DESIGN

HTML5

The Fundamentals Of Digital Marketing

Francis Enemuo

Frontend Developer

Lagos State, Nigeria

Summary

Specialize in training young people within high school and university on programming. My core languages include HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, and Python. I implemented a web database modelling using Flask as one of my core projects on Udacity Nanodegree.

Experience

Univelcity

Frontend Facilitator

January 2023 - Present (3 months)

Lagos, Lagos State, Nigeria

Frontend Instructor on HTML, CSS, JavaScript and React

Covenant Child Institute

Programming Tutor

June 2021 - January 2023 (1 year 8 months)

Lagos, Nigeria

EMBTEC KONZULTZ

Lead Trainer

January 2018 - January 2023 (5 years 1 month)

Lagos, Nigeria

Education

Udacity

Nanodegree, Computer Software Engineering (April 2022 - August 2022)

Udacity

Nanodegree, Full Stack Web Development · (2022)